我们想让FetchWeatherTask返回一个
We want the FetchWeatherTask to return an array
天气预报的字符串数组。这意味着我们需要
of string forecasts. That means we need to
改变AsyncTask的返回类型。
modify the return type of the AsyncTask.
然后在doInBackground()方法中，在我们读取
Then in the doInBackground method, after we've read
输入字符串后，我们实现这样的代码。
in the input string, we perform this code.
我们调用辅助方法getWeatherDataFromJson()，并且我们
We call the helper method getWeatherDataFromJson and we
传入返回的天气预报的JSON字符串，还有
pass in the forecastJson string as well as
预测的天数。我们在
the number of forecast days. We also catch
解析JSON的时候遇到任何问题都需要捕获相应的异常（这里是JSONException）。我们
any JSONExceptions if there's a problem with parsing. We
想验证天气预报的字符串数组是不是正确。
wanted to verify that the string array of forecast data
因此，在getWeatherDataFromJson()方法中，我们加入一些
is correct. So, within the getWeatherDataFromJson method, we added some
日志语句去输出数组的每个元素。
logging statements to print out each element of the array.